

+1 437 788 1280 jaspercheng2022@gmail.com Toronto, Canada

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jasper-cheng-501433243/

#### **Profile**

UI/UX Designer & Front End Developer with B.S. in computer science and a certificate from UofT SCS UX/UI Boot Camp. Skilled in most Adobe suite software, Figma, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and jQuery. Strengthed in user problem solving and believed that understanding the needs and frustrations is the key to improving user experience. Specializing in creating beautiful and functional websites and digital interfaces, I am a very passionate designer who always wants to grow, learn, and explore something new.

## **Experience**

#### YWI ALLIANCE INC.

MARKETING SPECIALIST

Sep 2020- April 2021

- Researched and analyzed related projects.
- Developed, implemented, and tracked marketing programs.
- Developed, created, and amended marketing materials.
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO) works

#### OFFICE MANAGER AND CUSTOMER SERVICE SUPERVISOR

Feb 2019 - Sep 2020

- Helped clients settling down in new country.
- · Acknowledged and resolved complaints.
- Kept records of interactions, transactions, comments, and complaints.
- Communicated and coordinated with colleagues.
- Ensured customer satisfaction and provide professional customer support.
- Provided feedbacks on the efficiency of the customer service process.
- Managed a team of junior customer service representatives.
- Solved emergent problems.
- Managed daily office maintenance.

### **NEO ENTERPISE INC.**

#### • BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

April 2017 - Feb 2019

- Sought locations for business.
- Communicated with local government and construction team regarding health and building permit registrations.

## **Porfolio Website Links**

https://hpyorange.github.io/JasperWeb/

## **Specialities**

Wed Design

User Interface

**User Experience** 

Wireframing

Prototyping

Front End Coding

## **Tools/Technologies**

Figma Sketch InVision

Adobe XD Illustrator AE

Photoshop Bootstrap 4/5

HTML5 CSS3 JS

#### **Hobbies**

Traveling

Tech Enthusiast

Video Gaming

- Communicated and coordinated with colleagues.
- Basic Business Interior designs.
- Graphic design works (poster, menu, wall painting)
- Sought suppliers and follow-up communicating.
- Pricing products.
- Looked for business cooperation opportunities.
- Related business researching.

### CUSTOMER SERVICE EXECTIVE · YWI ALLIANCE INC.

May 2016 - March 2017 (Part-Time)

• Helped clients settling down in new country.

### **Education**

# **Program Certificate - UI/UX Boot Camp**

2021- 2022  $\cdot$  University of Toronto School of Continuing Studies , Toronto

# **Graduation - Bachelor's in Computer Science**

2012 - 2017 · Brandon University, Brandon

- Major in Computer Science
- Minor in Fine Art

## Languages

English (Fluent)

Chinese (Mandarin) (Native)